Sergey Sudakovich

- sergey@sudakovich.com
- Linkedin
- Github

Summary

Software engineer and (in the past) web developer who has worked up and down the proverbial "full stack". I tend to be the jack of all trades when it comes to software development.

Skills

- Python, Groovy, Golang, Lua
- Jenkins, Ansible, Puppet, Docker, KVM, AWS
- Nginx, Apache, Gunicorn, uWSGI, Flask, Django
- MySQL, PostgeSQL, Redis, MongoDB
- Gradle, CMake

Experience

Member of Technical Staff at Cumulus Networks

June 2013 - Present

Lead developer of numerous parts of the Cumulus Linux ecosystem that include internal and external automation, software design and development and release engineering.

- \bullet maintain and improve platform test infrastucture, mainly Python based running on KVM
- created and continuously maintaining fully autonomous container-based CI/CD pipeline for infrastucture testing
- develop various tools and services used internally and externally, mainly Python and Golang based
- $\bullet\,$ integration with orchestration tools like Puppet, Ansible as well as new module development
- end-to-end automation of release process for Cumulus Linux, NetQ and other customer deliverables

Senior Software Engineer at Cisco Systems

June 2010 - June 2013

While part of the Cloud department, I participated in the following projects:

- developed initial version OpenStack Quantum Plugin for Nexus1000V
- worked on Nexus1000V & Microsoft SCVMM integration
- developed Nexus1000V visibility via VMware Web Client plugin
- implemented UCS Easy VM-FEX "hands-free" tool to migrate from VSwitch to Pass Through Switch (vDS) with in vCenter(VmWare) and UCSM(Cisco) infrastructure
- built UCSM Production cluster with iSCSI targets (WIndows Storage Server and FreeNAS)

Software Engineer II (intern) at Cisco Systems

May 2009 - August 2009

Implemented a Web Agent Prototype as a part of NOVA - next generation Cisco IOS, which allows interaction for a low level router code with a higher level metadata model; and adds Web UI interface to the router metadata modeling system. Most of the codebase is C and Python.

Web Developer at Hush-Hush Entertainment

August 2007 - July 2010

My primary roles as a web developer included:

- development and maintenance of internal and customer facing web portals and related tools
- automating post production content generation

As the only "IT-person" I took care of all IT-related things:

- hardware provisioning
- infrastructure provisioning and automation

Education

University of Southern California

MS in Computer Science with Specialization in Computer Networks, 2007
2009

- BS in Computer Science, 2007 - 2009